Bonowitz, Abraham J.; Papers apap186
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalty (NJADP), 2000-2012; 8; 1.2 cubic ft.
  - Journey Through Violence and Injustice event, 2006 November 5 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 49)
  - Seminary Baptist Church Journeys Through Violence and Injustice Event Program, 2006 November 5 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 50)
  - NJADP Call for Volunteers Letter, 2006 November 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 51)
  - NJADP Speaker Event Flyer, 2006 November 30 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 52)
  - Monteliar High School Mock Committee Invitation, 2006 December 5 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 53)
  - Update Letter for NJADP Member District 38, 2006 December 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 54)
  - Thank You to A. Bonowitz from Alice Vearney for Talk given to youth group, 2006 December 14 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 55)
  - NJADP Letters to district members asking them to Thank Representatives for passing A-795, 2006 December 18 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 56)
  - Update letter for NJADP Members District 36, 2006 December 18 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 57)
  - Diocese of NJ 2007 Concention NJADP Exhibit Registration, 2006 December 19 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 58)
  - NJADP Hispanic Outreach, 2006 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 59)
  - NJADP Press Release, 2006 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 60)
  - Assorted Testimonies before The New Jersey Senate Judiciary Committee Concerning The Death Penalty, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 61)
  - Journeys through Violence and Injustice Speaker event flyers, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 62)
  - NJADP Event bookings, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 63)
  - Amnesty International and NJ.com articles regarding abolition recommendation of State Comission, 2007 January 2 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 64)
  - List of Organizations to Solicit for letters to Legislature, 2007 January 6 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 65)
  - NJADP Email re: Performance of "The Exonerated", 2007 January 15 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 66)
  - Assemblyman Jack Connors to A. Bonowitz Re: Bill 795 to repeal DP, 2007 January 24 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 67)
  - Shawn Rondinella to A. Bonowitz Re: Setan Hall Prep School Event, 2007 January 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 68)
  - NJADP Catholic Church and The Death Penalty Flyer, 2007 January (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 69)
  - NJADP Membership Mailings, 2007 January-March (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 70)
  - NJ Death Penalty Study Commission Report, 2007 January (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 71)
  - NJADP Schedule of Upcoming Events, 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 72)
  - Ray Krone event material, 2007 February 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 73)
  - Kirk Blood worth Speaker event, Amnesty international/NJADP, 2007 February 9 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 74)
  - Union for reform Judaism List of current issues, 2007 February 20 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 75)
  - Manasquan voices of Experience Event, 2007 March 24 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 76)
  - Toms River Voices of Experience Event, 2007 March 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 77)
  - Emails regarding progress of ACLU letter campaign, 2007 March; 2007 April (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 78)
  - Justice for All Awards Dinner, 2007 March; 2007 April (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 79)
  - "Voices That Challenge," No. 4, 2007 April (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 80)
  - Letter from Kirk Bloodsworth to Cardinal McCarrich Re: Support for NJADP Campaign, 2007 May 1 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 81)
  - NJADP Memorandum to Senator Lesniak, 2007 May 7 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 82)
  - News Article Concerning NJ Abolition Campaign, 2007 May 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 83)
  - United Methodists Death Penalty Resolution, 2007 May 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 84)
  - "The Road not Considered: Revising New Jersey's Death Penalty", 2007 May 10 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 85)
  - NJ Senate Judicary Committee Notice Re: Committee Meeting and copy of Bill S-171, 2007 May 10 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 86)
  - Letter from Celeste Fitzgerald to Senator James Re: Bill S-171/A795, 2007 May 24 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 87)
  - NJADP Staff Meeting, 2007 May 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 88)
  - Scheduling NJADP Outreach to Amnesty Groups, 2007 May 30 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 89)
  - Letter from NJ Homocide Survivors to Senate Judiciary Committee, 2007 May (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 90)
  - "News and Views" New Jersey Association on Correction, 2007 Spring-Winter (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 91)
  - NJADP Draft Interim Report to Atlantic Philantropies, 2007 June 21 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 92)
  - Respect Life Ministry Voices of Experience event and related emails, 2007 August-October (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 93)
  - Request to NJADP for a Speaker at Confirmation Class, 2007 September 12 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 94)
  - Executive Committee Contacts List NJADP, 2007 September 11 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 95)
  - Camden Racial Justice Committee Event organizer emails, 2007 September 17 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 96)
  - Nj Legislative Roster 2006-2007 By District, 2007 October 1 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 97)
  - Sr. Helen Prejean event at The College of New Jersey, 2007 October 2; 2007 October 3 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 98)
  - A. Bonowitz Symposium on Crime and Justice Registration Material, 2007 October 6; 2007 October 7 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 99)
  - Thomas Kelaher to Celeste Fitzgerald, 2007 October 9 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 100)
  - October NJADP mailings Timetable, 2007 October 11 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 101)
  - NJADP Schedule of Upcoming Events, 2007 October 12 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 102)
  - Rabb: letter campaign material, 2007 October 15 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 103)
  - NJADP Letter to New Jersey Clergy, 2007 October 24 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 104)
  - League of Women Voters Death Penalty Letter Writing event, 2007 October 30 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 105)
  - Legislature Voting Projections and fall priorities lists NJADP, 2007 October (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 106)
  - Sr. Helen Prejean Speaker Event, 2007 November 8 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 107)
  - Talking points for Celeste Fitzgerald, 2007 November 9 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 108)
  - Letters to NJADP Members regarding District Representatives, 2007 November 12 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 109)
  - League of Women Voters Death Penalty Event, 2007 November 14 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 110)
  - List of Unsolicited Organizations to Target for Lesgislative mailings, 2007 November 16 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 111)
  - NJADP Schedule of Upcoming Events, 2007 November 27 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 112)
  - Religious Communities of New Jersey Letter to the Legislature, 2007 November 27 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 113)
  - New Jersey Rabbis for Alternatives to the Death Penalty letter to Legislature and event flyer, 2007 November 29 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 114)
  - Filled out responses from New Jersey Rabbis to NJADP, 2007 November (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 115)
  - NJADP Affiliafe and Member Letters to Governor John Corzine, 2007 November (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 116)
  - Testimonies against The Death Penalty to The New Jersey Budget Committee, 2007 December 3 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 117)
  - Victims families and the Death Penalty Testimony to the New Jersey and Public Safety Committee, 2007 December 10 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 118)
  - "We're in the Homestretch!" NJADP mailing, 2007 December (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 119)
  - "An overwhelming consensus: Replace the Death Penalty with Life without Parole", 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 120)
  - Dead Man Walking event flyers, 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 121)
  - New Jersey letter writing campaign organizational materials, 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 122)
  - New Jersey Rabbis for Alternatives to the DP Material, 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 123)
  - Organization letters advocating for DP Aboliton, 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 124)
  - Representative Addresses for District letter campaigns, 2007 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 125)
  - International Death Penalty Abolition Day Save the date mailings and invite list, 2008 January; 2008 February (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 126)
  - NJADP Post Abolition letter to members, 2008 February 4 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 127)
  - War Memorial Abolition Celebration, 2008 February -March (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 128)
  - "Legislation, Litigation, Reflection, and Repeal" Seton Hall University School of Law event material, 2008 April 14 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 129)
  - "Abolishing The Death Penalty in New Jersey: A compilation of Speeches Letters, and Articles", 2008 (Box 1 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 130)
  - NJADP List of Services for Homicide and Sudden Death Survivors, 2012 July 25 (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 1)
  - District- Specific Action Flyers, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 2)
  - For Whom the Bell Tolls Pamphlet, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 3)
  - "From Lynch Mobs to the Killing State" Event Flyer, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 4)
  - Governmental Affairs Agent Registration, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 5)
  - Innocence Lost in New Jersey Draft Document, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 6)
  - Journey Through Violence and Injustice (JTVI) Upcoming Events Press Release, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 7)
  - Letter to New Jersey State Legislature from Former Prosecutors, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 8)
  - Murder Victims Families Draft Letter to Legislature, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 9)
  - "New Jersey's Death Penalty: A Broken System", Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 10)
  - NJADP Announcement Flyer, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 11)
  - NJADP Draft Member Mailing with Excerpt of Larry Post Letter, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 12)
  - NJADP Informational Brochures, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 13)
  - NJADP Letter Campaign Mailings, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 14)
  - NJADP Post-Abolution To-Do List, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 15)
  - "Organizations Calling for an And to the Death Penalty in New Jersey", Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 16)
  - Step-By-Step Petition Instructions for Members and Affiliates, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 17)
  - "We Did It" Post-Abolution NJADP Mailing, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 18)
  - "We're in the Homestretch" Mailings, Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 19)
  - "What Should We Do About New Jersey's Death Penalty?", Undated (Box 2 (8-New Jerseyans for Alternatives to the Death Penalt), Folder 20)
- Murder Victims Families for Reconciliation (MVFR) Exhibit Not in Our Name, 1983-2015; 9; 42 cubic ft.
  Arranged Alphabetically. Title Posters First.
  Not in Our Name was a travelling poster exhibit of first hand accounts by vicitims and others affected by the death penalty. The exhibit was organized by activist group Murder Victims' Families for Reconciliation. The title posters from the exhibit are ordered first in the series then followed by each story board.
  - Title Poster 1- About this Exhibit, Undated (Flat-file 1, Folder 1)
  - Title Poster 2- Not in Our Name, Undated (Flat-file 2, Folder 2)
  - Title Poster 3-Murder Victim's Families for Roconcilation Policy Recommendations, Undated (Flat-file 3, Folder 3)
  - Policy Recommendations 1-5, Undated (Flat-file 4, Folder 4)
  - Policy Recommendations 6-9, Undated (Flat-file 5, Folder 5)
  - Title Poster 4- Crime Victims Equality Act, Undated (Flat-file 6, Folder 6)
  - Avery, Michael, Undated (Flat-file 7, Folder 7)
  - Babbitt, Bill, Undated (Flat-file 8, Folder 8)
  - Bane, Pat, Undated (Flat-file 9, Folder 9)
  - Bankston, Sadie, Undated (Flat-file 10, Folder 10)
  - Bishop, Jeanne & Jennifer, Undated (Flat-file 11, Folder 11)
  - Black, Susie & Hector, Undated (Flat-file 12, Folder 12)
  - Boscoe, Antoinette, Undated (Flat-file 13, Folder 13)
  - Bosler, Suezann, Undated (Flat-file 14, Folder 14)
  - Burgin, Peggy, Undated (Flat-file 15, Folder 15)
  - Byars, Carol, Undated (Flat-file 16, Folder 16)
  - Callen, Ron & Carolyn, Undated (Flat-file 17, Folder 17)
  - Carlson, Ron, Undated (Flat-file 18, Folder 18)
  - Chery, Tina, Undated (Flat-file 19, Folder 19)
  - Clark, Pat, Undated (Flat-file 20, Folder 20)
  - Cochran, Shirley, Undated (Flat-file 21, Folder 21)
  - Coleman, Anne, Undated (Flat-file 22, Folder 22)
  - Coleman, Charisse, Undated (Flat-file 23, Folder 23)
  - Cook, Kerry Max, Undated (Flat-file 24, Folder 24)
  - Crawford, Pam, Undated (Flat-file 25, Folder 25)
  - Curley, Robert, Undated (Flat-file 26, Folder 26)
  - Cushing,Renny, Undated (Flat-file 27, Folder 27)
  - Deans, Marie & Robert, Undated (Flat-file 28, Folder 28)
  - Dickens, Shirley, Undated (Flat-file 29, Folder 29)
  - Dicks, Trevor, Undated (Flat-file 30, Folder 30)
  - Dillon, Kathy, Undated (Flat-file 31, Folder 31)
  - Dixon, Celeste, Undated (Flat-file 32, Folder 32)
  - Ducanson, Carol, Undated (Flat-file 33, Folder 33)
  - Eason, Leigh, Undated (Flat-file 34, Folder 34)
  - Everett, Walter, Undated (Flat-file 35, Folder 35)
  - Floyd, Felicia, Undated (Flat-file 36, Folder 36)
  - Gauger, Gary & Ginger, Undated (Flat-file 37, Folder 37)
  - Gayle, Aba, Undated (Flat-file 38, Folder 38)
  - Giger, Michelle, Undated (Flat-file 39, Folder 39)
  - Gilbert, Ruby, Undated (Flat-file 40, Folder 40)
  - Gillihan, Ron, Undated (Flat-file 41, Folder 41)
  - Gowen, Nancy, Undated (Flat-file 42, Folder 42)
  - Guard, David, Undated (Flat-file 43, Folder 43)
  - Heller, Henry, Undated (Flat-file 44, Folder 44)
  - Hines, Maria, Undated (Flat-file 45, Folder 45)
  - Hotchkiss, Phyllis, Undated (Flat-file 46, Folder 46)
  - Jacobs, Sonia "Sunny", Undated (Flat-file 47, Folder 47)
  - James, Ernest, Undated (Flat-file 48, Folder 48)
  - Jenkins, Bill, Undated (Flat-file 49, Folder 49)
  - Khasmisa, Azim, Undated (Flat-file 50, Folder 50)
  - Lamm, Gus, Undated (Flat-file 51, Folder 51)
  - Lane, Marietta Jaeger, Undated (Flat-file 52, Folder 52)
  - Lewis, Barbara, Undated (Flat-file 53, Folder 53)
  - Lowenstien, Kate & Tom, Undated (Flat-file 54, Folder 54)
  - Lucero, Bill, Undated (Flat-file 55, Folder 55)
  - Malo, Eve, Undated (Flat-file 56, Folder 56)
  - Mathis, Teresa, Undated (Flat-file 57, Folder 57)
  - Mayberry, Billie Jean, Undated (Flat-file 58, Folder 58)
  - McCoy, Pat, Undated (Flat-file 59, Folder 59)
  - Melendez, Juan Roberto, Undated (Flat-file 60, Folder 60)
  - MURF Board, Undated (Flat-file 61, Folder 61)
  - Norton, Sue, Undated (Flat-file 62, Folder 62)
  - Oberweis, Julia Ann, Undated (Flat-file 63, Folder 63)
  - Pajama, Helen, Undated (Flat-file 64, Folder 64)
  - Pelke, Bill, Undated (Flat-file 65, Folder 65)
  - Post, Lorry & June, Undated (Flat-file 66, Folder 66)
  - Richards, Sushine, Undated (Flat-file 67, Folder 67)
  - Rivera-Huitron,, Yvonne, Undated (Flat-file 68, Folder 68)
  - Roberts, Brian, Undated (Flat-file 69, Folder 69)
  - Robinson, Ken & Lois, Undated (Flat-file 70, Folder 70)
  - Rockefeller, Terry Kay, Undated (Flat-file 71, Folder 71)
  - Rodriguez, Phyllis & Orlando, Undated (Flat-file 72, Folder 72)
  - Schneider, Karen, Undated (Flat-file 73, Folder 73)
  - Seidler, Miriam, Undated (Flat-file 74, Folder 74)
  - Senior, Sally, Undated (Flat-file 75, Folder 75)
  - Sheppard, Sam Resse, Undated (Flat-file 76, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Kristi, Undated (Flat-file 77, Folder 77)
  - Sojoodi, Joy, Undated (Flat-file 78, Folder 78)
  - Supreme Court Poster, Undated (Flat-file 79, Folder 79)
  - Welch, Bud, Undated (Flat-file 80, Folder 80)
  - White, George W., Undated (Flat-file 81, Folder 81)
  - Villalobos, Ricardo, Undated (Flat-file 82, Folder 82)
  - Williams, Dale, Undated (Flat-file 83, Folder 83)
  - Wormack-Keels, Renee, Undated (Flat-file 84, Folder 84)
- Subject Files, 1983-2013; 10; no; cubic ft.
  This series contains announcements, conference materials, court documents, journals articles, mailings, news clippings, newsletters, personal calendars, and reports about the death penalty and the progress of abolitionists. The series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Abolition Action Committee (AAC) Fast and Vigil Announcement, 1997 May 7 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Abolition Action Committee (AAC) Fast and Vigil Announcement, 2000 May 12 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Abolition Action Committee (AAC) Starvin' For Justice 12th Annual Fast and Vigil Announcement, 2005 June (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Abolition Action Committee (AAC) Starvin' For Justice 2006 Sponsorship Forms (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Abolition Action Committee (AAC) Starvin' For Justice Fast and Vigil - Planning Folder, 2007 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Abolition Tour 2004 Certificate of Appreciation to Abe Bonowitz, 2004 February 24 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Against the Death Penalty Graphics, Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 2005 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - American Civil Liberties Union of Florida, 2003 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - "Any Yanks (But Lawyers) Getting Their Money Out of Death Row?" by Meredith Walker, 1996 December 26 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - "Arbitrary Capricious Discriminatory 30 Years After Gregg v. Georgia Grassroots Organizing Kit", 2006 May (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Arizona Lawsuit, 2002 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Arrest Record and Material from North Carolina Vigil, 2005 December - 2006 February (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Background Information for Death Penalty Meetings, 2007 July 8 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Biblical Teaching on Capital Punishment - The Old Testament: Moral Seriousness But "Do Not Kill", Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham Motion to Proceed in Forma Pauperis on Petition for Writ of Certori, 2000 March 8 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Bonowitz, Abraham Release Order Addendum, 2002 January 2 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Breaking the Cycle of Violence: An Issue Packet on Abolishing the Death Penalty, Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Bush, Jeb, 2003 October 23; 2004 January 3 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Business Cards with Annotations [1 of 2], Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Business Cards with Annotations [2 of 2], Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Capital Case Defense Seminar "Human Beings and Human Rights", 2004 February 13-16 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Capital Punishment on the 25th Anniversary of Furman v. Georgia - A Report by the Southern Center for Human Rights, Stephen B. Bright, Director, 1997 June 26 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Case Histories: A Review of 23 Individuals Released from Death Row, Florida Commission on Capital Cases, 2002 June 20 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - A Caseload / Workload Formula for Florida's Office of the Capital Collateral Representative, 1987 February (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Catholics Against Capital Punishment, 2003 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Catholic Mobilizing Network, Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Catholic Mobilizing Network Meeting Minutes, 2003 September 17 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Chay'im Ben-Shalom, 1995 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Cesar Chavez From in the Footsteps of Ghandi, Undated (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Cesar E. Chavez Foundation Informational Packet, 1995 (Box 1 (10-Subject Files), Folder 31)